A Guide to the Correspondence and Subject Files of the Director of the Virginia Dept. of General Services, 1974-2014
Library of Virginia
- Series I. Correspondence and Subject Files, 1974-2007., Extent: 23 cu. ft. (23 boxes).
  - Accession 32690, 1977-1982.
    - Land Management, 1982. (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Land Management #4, 1981. (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Leases, 1982. (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Legislation, 1979-1980. (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Legislative Implementation Report, 1980. (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - Listing of DGS Directives Reports Made by and to DGS, 1981. (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Management Analysis and Systems Development, 1981. (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - Miscellaneous, 1982. (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - National Conference of General Services Officers, July-December 1978. (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - National Conference of General Services Officers, September 1981. (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - National Conference of General Services Officers--Des Moines, Iowa, August 18-August 20, 1980. (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - National Conference of State General Services Officers--Annapolis, MD, September 26-September 29, 1979. (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - National Conference of State General Services Officers--Annual Meeting, Charleston, SC, 1977. (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - National Conference of State General Services Officers Executive Committee, 1981. (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - NCOGSO--Cost Reduction Responses, 1981. (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - NCSGSO--Problems Unique to DGS Operation, 1982. (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Office of Risk Management #2, 1980. (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Old DMV Building, 1980. (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Parking Deck 9th and Franklin Streets, 1981. (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - P R and I--Blanket Bond and Workmen's Compensation, 1979. (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - P R and I Blanket Bond Program, 1981. (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - P R and I Joint Subcommittee on Insurance, 1979. (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Procurement Law, 1981. (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Procurement Management Review, 1982. (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Procurement Speech, August 16, 1982. (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Procurement Study Joint Subcommittee Draft, 1981. (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Procurement Study Public Hearings, June 9-June 11, 1981. (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Procurement Study--Robert P. Kyle, 1980. (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Product Testing, 1980. (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Productivity Improvement Projects, 1981. (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Professional Organizations, 1981. (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Property Records and Insurance, 1978. (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Proposed Legislation, 1981. (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - P and S, 1979. (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - P and S, 1981. (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - P and S, 1982. (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - P and S Contract Section, 1979. (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - P and S Forms Management, 1978. (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - P and S Hearing and Investigation, 1981. (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - P and S James Madison Printing Press, 1980. (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - P and S Mail and Messenger Services, 1981. (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - P and S Management Team, 1979. (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - P and S Manuals, 1979. (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - P and S Paging System, 1980. (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - P and S Procurement Study, 1979. (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - P and S Purchasing Section, 1978. (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - P and S Surplus Property, 1981. (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Publications, 1981. (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - Purchases and Supply, 1980. (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Report to Board, April 29, 1980. (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Review of A and F Directives, 1979. (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Risk Management, 1982. (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Risk Management #3, 1982. (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Risk Management Advisory Committee Report to Joint Subcommittee, December 1978. (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Risk Management Bid Package, 1981. (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Risk Management Delay in Implementation, 1981. (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Risk Management Insurance Board #2, 1981. (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - S.B. 689--Public Building Authority, 1979. (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Senate Joint Resolution 58, 1978. (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - Southeast and Northeast States Conference on Capital Outlay and Construction Administration, August 14, 1978. (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Space, 1982. (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - State Office Furniture Advisory Committee, 1979. (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Supreme Court Building, 1982. (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Tort Claims, 1982. (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Vehicle Self-Insurance Program, 1982. (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - VEPCO Contract, 1980. (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - VEPCO Contract, 1980. (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - VEPCO Negotiations, 1982. (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - VEPCO Original Electric Contracts, 1976. (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - VIMS, 1980. (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Virginia Electric and Power Company Negotiations, 1980. (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Workmen's Compensation, 1981. (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Workmen's Compensation Billings, 1982. (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Worker's Compensation Insurance Program, 1982. (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Accession 50089, 2003-2005.
    - James T. Roberts, Director--Correspondence, May 2003-December 2005. (Box 1)
  - Accession 50788, 1978-2007.
    - Douglas Hamner correspondence, 1978-1985. (Box 1)
    - Wendell Seldon correspondence, 1986-1991. (Box 1)
    - Raymond Patterson correspondence, 1992. (Box 1)
    - Donald Williams correspondence, 1998-2001. (Box 1)
    - Demerst B. Smit correspondence, 2002-2003. (Box 1)
    - Richard F. Silwoski correspondence, 2006 January-March. (Box 1)
    - Richard F. Silwoski correspondence, 2006 April-June. (Box 1)
    - Richard F. Silwoski correspondence, 2006 July-September. (Box 1)
    - Richard F. Silwoski correspondence, 2006 October-December. (Box 1)
    - Richard F. Silwoski correspondence, 2007 January-March. (Box 1)
    - Richard F. Silwoski correspondence, 2007 April-June. (Box 1)
    - Richard F. Silwoski correspondence, 2007 July-September. (Box 1)
    - Richard F. Silwoski correspondence, 2007 October-December. (Box 1)
  - Accession 50954, 2000.
    This subseries contains videotapes of episodes of Bob Vila's "This Old House," which documents the restoration of the Executive Mansion.
  - Accession 51588, 2008-2011.
    - Correspondence of Director Richard F. Sliwoski, 2008-2011. (Box 1)
  - Accession 51723, 2008-2011.
    - Correspondence of Director Richard F. Sliwoski, 2012-2014. (Box 1)